[music]
Hey, hey,
hey, hey.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Well, good morning everyone and welcome
to the Fiber Broadband Association's
Fiverr for breakfast. We're now in our
first episode of 2026
and wow, you know, a huge crowd. So,
either everybody's excited to be back
for work in 2026 or Katherine just has a
ton of friends, which is probably the
latter. Um, but before we kick off, I'd
like to thank Wesco, the platinum
sponsor of Five for Breakfast. You know,
I hope everybody had just a wonderful
holiday and ready to get back to work
because 2026 is going to be the biggest
year ever for the fiber broadband
industry. You know, I could not be more
excited. In Washington, Congress is
officially back in session and both the
House and Senate are kicking off the
year at a fast pace with a a major
government funding deadline looming on
January 30th. You know, this week
lawmakers are expected to take up three
bill funding package which will include
the Interior and Environmental, Energy,
Water Development, and Commerce,
Justice, and Science, which includes
funding 51 million to fund NTIA through
September 30th of the year. And the
appropriations package directs NTI to
update appropriators on its plans and
timelines for spending the remaining
bead funds within 30 days of enactment
of this bill to ensure that all be
programs grants comply with the IJ uh
ban on rate regulation. Ahead of the
holiday recess, we uh want to note that
representatives Andy Bar and Hal Rogers
introduced the House Companion to the
Successful BE act providing guidance on
the bead non-deployment funds. So FBA is
very supportive of this legislation.
On the NTI bead front, 53 out of 56
states and territories have submitted
their final proposals for NTI review.
And as of, you know, near the end of the
year last year, NTI had approved final
proposals for 37 of the 56 states and
territories. So finally, we're starting
to get there. Um, so the Fiber Broadband
Association will be kicking off our
regional fiber connect workshops in
Oklahoma City on Thursday, February 5th
at the Okana Resort with a focus on
tribal broadband. You're not going to
want to miss that. And after our tribal
broadband regional event, we'll be in
Washington DC on February 24th and 25th
for our public policy summit and DC
flyin. This has always been an amazing
event for our members to engage with
Congress and the administration and key
agencies such as the FCC and NTI. So, I
look forward to seeing you there.
And last week on Fiber for Breakfast on
New Year's Eve, our guest was the Fiber
Broadband Association's 2026 chairwoman
Ash Brown who discussed her plans and
vision for the Fiber Broadman
Association and our industry for this
coming year. So, if you missed that
session, you can go to our website and
watch the replay. Today on Fire for
Breakfast, our guest is Katherine Dwit,
the director of the Pew Charitable Trust
Broadband Access Initiative, discuss new
year, new connections, speed meets
forward in 2026.
So, Katherine directs Pew's broadband
access initiative, which works to
accelerate efforts to connect millions
of Americans to affordable, reliable,
high-speed internet. In addition to
working with policy makers, researchers,
and other stakeholders to improve policy
outcomes, DWIT's work also includes
addressing research gaps and bringing
together stakeholders for datadriven
discussions about how to ensure that
every American benefits from universal
connectivity. Before joining Pew,
Katherine was an associate with Booze
Allen Hamilton where she focused on
broadband deployment, organizational
management, and public affairs. She's
also a senior fellow with the Hines
Endowment leading projects on youth
philanthropy and community engagement.
Katherine holds a bachelor degree in
communications and sociology from Penn
State and a master's in public
administration from the University of
Pittsburgh. Welcome, Katherine. Always
great to see you. Glad to have you here.
And for our audience, please type in
your questions. And oh, we're already
starting to get questions. So great. So
type in your questions and we'll work
those into the discussion. So, happy new
year, Katherine. Glad to see you always.
Um,
>> happy new year, Gary.
>> Yeah. Um, can we start off with a little
bit about, you know, Pew Pew Charitable
Trust and its mission? Like, what is
this all about?
>> Sure. Uh, so Pew, thank you again for
having me. First episode of the year.
I'm honored. Uh, and it is going to be a
big year. Uh, so I'm excited to uh come
and talk to you all about that. Um, as
for those who aren't familiar with Pew,
we're a nonprofit, uh, nonpartisan
research organization. So, uh, God love
you, Gary, for reading that long bio,
but what Gary said is true. Uh, my job
and, uh, those of my colleagues here is
to bring, uh, data and research to help
policy makers solve complex challenges.
And my team has been focused on
broadband since 2018. And uh states in
particular really sit at the core of
Pew's work, not just the broadband
portfolio. And um we work closely with
state legislators, governors, officials
all across the country uh again on
issues from fiscal health to
environmental um environmental
protection and housing. My team uh
started its work in 2018 uh working on a
research project to understand what
states were doing uh on the digital
divide. How are they focusing on
deployment and that research uh led to
much of the work that we do with state
officials today including on bead.
>> Well, fantastic. Um so tell me a little
bit about Betty. What is that and how is
that is that still going on and you guys
still engaged with all the SPOS's? Yeah,
still going on. Thank you. Uh that's a
peer learning network for state
broadband offices. Um one thing that a
lot of folks don't realize uh is unless
you have the good fortune of being
steeped in this day-to-day uh is that
there is no professional association for
state broadband officials. Uh so when uh
the American Rescue Plan Act was passed
and the capital projects fund was
established, all of a sudden state more
than half the states were standing up
new broadband offices and looking for
help and support and guidance. Where do
we go? What do we do? And then the
infrastructure bill passed shortly
thereafter. So since um August of 2021,
uh Pew has been working uh with running
this program called Betty. It's the
broadband education and training
initiative and it really is a peer
learning network for these state
broadband offices and uh we do custom
research analysis and really it's
honestly Gary it's about providing
support for these really uh brilliant
and scrappy public officials to learn
from one another and share information
and have a space to um really come up
with uh creative and relevant solutions
that will work for their communities. So
we'll continue doing that work in the
years to come. Uh I think it will be
very important as bead rolls out. Um and
we also use the work that we do through
Betty. Um it informs our research that
we do generally on universal access. Um
it led to the research that we did on
workforce and permitting which I'm sure
we'll talk about later. And then uh we
also uh do a lot of time educating
public officials just helping
legislators, governors um understand
what the what is with bead and why
broadband deployment is challenging uh
and what their state offices need to to
be successful.
>> Awesome. I mean the one thing I can say
about be uh the one thing it has done is
um create a state broadband office in
every you know all 56 states and
territories and I have to say my
experience you know we go around the
country in our regional events we always
have the state broadband office there
and usually the governor or someone from
the governor's office and every state
broadband office that we work with has
been amazing you know these guys work
their tails off and just do amazing jobs
so I know that the biggest when I talked
the state broadband directors, you know,
the biggest challenge is to to know
what's going on and they really lean on
you and your organization to kind of
help connect them with all the other
offices. Is that kind of what you're
seeing?
>> Uh, thank you. That that's incredibly
kind. Um, the Yes, they do. Uh, the
directors and their staff uh really do
work with us um and use that space um
for two things, I think. One is just
again that information sharing between
practitioners. Um you you know how
important just being able to sit down
and say, "Okay, here's what I'm hearing.
What are you hearing? What do we do
about it?" Um but it's also creating
spaces for um folks in uh certain roles
like grants management or permitting,
those staff level functions that um
really benefit from learning for one
another. um they all kind of break off
into their own little cohorts and then
can trade practices uh and um approaches
in that way. And I I think what to your
point um it's been really exciting to
see the growth of state broadband
offices and staff over the last few
years and I don't mean growth in like
the size although let's be clear
broadband offices need to be a certain
size in order to administer all these
funds well um and according uh to policy
um but just the technical expertise that
they're building their fluency in uh
matters of deployment and adoption and
digital skills ing and the ideas coming
out of these offices to solve some of
the long-standing issues for deployment
and um again adoption affordability. Um
it's really exciting and I think that um
bead is going to offer us a unique
opportunity to learn
both about um improving policy outcomes
but how do we really approach universal
access deploying high-speed affordable
reliable internet that's going to last
decades in the future? How do we do that
well? How do we do that in a way that
serves uh the public good and
constituent needs while also working
very closely with the private sector to
ensure that those bottom lines are met?
And we are I think standing on the
precipice of a really important moment
um in research which you can tell that's
what I do for a living uh but also in
policy and thinking about where do we go
from here because the landscape is going
to look different in four years than it
does today.
>> All right. So, you know, back gosh, 50
months ago, 50 50 months ago when the
IIJA
was signed into law,
>> you know, 15
>> 50 months, right?
>> Um, that's a lifetime.
>> So, there was 15.2 million unserved and
underserved locations. And so, then when
we finally got around to the benefit of
the bargain round, we ended up with 4.2
million. So programs like um Joey
Wender's Treasury um capital projects
fund, they got $10 billion out the door
with four people and ARPA and private
investment. You know, we've been able to
get 11 million of these um locations
served before bead even has a shovel in
the ground. So is bead still a big deal?
I mean does that should we even care
about
>> I'm sorry I'm I'm smiling uh because
this question comes up so often
[laughter]
and uh the answer is yes uh it matters
for a few reasons and the first is you
of all people and your members know that
the folks who are currently left offline
and unserved they are the hardest and
most expensive to reach when we're
talking about the business case for
connecting unserved Americans
This is why this infusion of public
capital is critical because otherwise
there there is no business case to
connect these households. And to your
point where we have seen over the last
several years where that infusion of
public funds can really accelerate
buildout um and incentivize the
deployment of um uh connections that are
going to last longer and be more useful
in the future. Um [clears throat] and I
think that the um actually I'll just
stop there. Yes. Yes, it is still
important.
>> Well, you know, certainly um you know,
we're excited that we're finally finally
finally have um final appro approvals um
out there. One of the questions come
that um from the audience is okay NIST
you we saw last year at this time you
know we had three states approved and we
thought we're going to move forward and
then they got hung up on NIST. Uh so the
question is will NIS start approving
more states now?
>> Uh that is not necessarily a question
for me but rather our partners in the in
the public sector and the federal level.
I I think though the point is one people
actually know that NIST is involved. And
I I think that I I I flag this not to be
uh pedantic but rather I think that one
of the differences and I think one of
the advantages of where we are today
versus five years ago is that folks have
more fluency in this issue. They have
more lawmakers,
partners in the private sector,
advocates, researchers. They understand
deployment and universal access and
policy very differently than they did 5
years ago. That's a good thing. So the
fact that someone is saying and asking a
question about NIST, can we expect NIST
to move faster? I don't really think
that's a question many people would have
thought to bring up on a podcast like
this five years ago. All that to say,
what I think we what I hope we will
focus on in the years to come is this
public pressure. making sure that
because we've got four years to build
once those plans are once all the
documents are signed and there are
several documents we could talk about
those there that's a four-year
construction deadline and in order for
that four-year deadline to be met
everything has to work in sequence and
be on time so we need to make sure that
states the private sector communities
are working at the table with federal
partners and NTIA all working together
to say this is what's working, this is
what's not working, how do we solve it?
Uh, so I think that this is my
roundabout way of saying I hope that
NIST will continue to approve things
quickly. Um, but I think the more um
public attention and accountability and
that we can draw to some of these um
procedural [clears throat] barriers or
procedural delays, that's not what I'm
calling NIST right now, just generally,
um, the better off we'll be and the more
likely we'll be able to deploy all those
funds on time. uh and according to plan.
>> You know, actually I asked this question
to assistant secretary Roth last time I
saw her last month and um you know
because LA this time last year Venice
from Louisiana was calling me up like
Gary, how do I get this NIST approve?
You know, no one even knew that NIST had
to approve. You know, when you go look
through the say, oh yeah, N has to
approve commerce stuff.
>> It was more of a a surprise, but that
was really to kind of hold things up.
And uh what assistant secretary Ross
said is that they the NIST approvals
will go very very quick because
everybody's aligned. You know the
secretary of commerce LNI is you know
this is his plan. This is things need to
move forward. So I don't think we'll see
any problems with NIST approvals and you
know we already start seen states that
are getting ready to put shovels in the
ground. So um interesting question.
Here's another I'll call it red herring.
All right. So right before the holidays,
the GAO decision on B337604
came out and basically said procedural
error on the way we did the benefit of
the or we commerce did benefit of the
bargain. Um,
I have an opinion on on what that means,
but I don't know if you have any
thoughts on that.
>> I don't uh I think the um it's important
for Congress to know that that was
released, but no, I don't have a I don't
have an uh No, I don't have an answer on
that right now.
>> Yeah. So, we've you know, of course, as
soon as that came out, um you know, the
the concern was is this going to hold
everything up? Are we going to have to
redo everything? And our assessment is
this is kind of a commerce to just say
whoops and let's file the you know
paperwork and and so forth because I
don't think there's any appetite
um by the administration or congress to
slow down this pep deployment. It's
already we're only year five and uh we
need to move forward. So um anyway so I
think that's something not to worry
about.
>> Yeah Gary I think you're hitting on um
both in that and talking about NIS as
well. Um
there is bipartisan
support for this program to get moving
and there is it is in the there's a
political interest here as well. I mean
I I think um your members probably know
this better than most like constituents
care about broadband. I mean state and
local officials um uh Christine Hulquist
from uh the state director for Vermont
ran on broadband when she was running
for governor. So, you know, they there
is a political motivation here for the
funds to get moving and shovels in the
ground as quickly as possible. So, I
would agree with you that uh there's
there's little appetite for continued
delay.
>> It's it's great though that we all are
starting to learn these little tiny
obscure, you know, things like the GAO
and and and NIST and so forth. But yeah,
we're we've been living bead way too
long. U so another question I'll take
this one but it's all right how can we
be sure that 2026 is going to be a great
year for fiber you know and they said we
believed this in the past didn't happen
what's different now than a couple years
ago and I mean I can tell you that um
you know I've been modeling uh fiber
deployment and I looking at I my model
basically said that we can get to about
12 million homes passed per year and
then we'll run into supply a little bit
of supply chain but more uh workforce
development because we can't grow the
workforce fast enough. We hit 11.8
million homes pass last year and this
was largely private investment. um you
know the federal and state funding the
um government funding is just a small
part less than 10% of the overall capex
for fiber and it's been going crazy and
now fueled by AI infrastructure and
again another huge initiative for the
administration and so uh fiber is going
to be we're going to blow past you know
so we grew over 10% about 11% last year
u we've been growing at about that rate
for the last few years And um yes, so we
are definitely going to blow through my
model for 2026. And it it's really
exciting and that's what we've really
seen is so one of the things the
administration did do is you know
whether you think the one big beautiful
bill good bad ugly it did have a tax
provision and provided 100% bonus
depreciation which is been is created
about uh four to5 billion dollars of
private investment free cash flow for
fiber just for fiber and that and we saw
AT&T immediately sign up for another
million homes per year passed um of
there getting to now 64 million homes
passed with fiber. Um and again it's
just um that really fueled helped fuel
private investment. So with that let's
get back to Katherine and um all right
so let's talk about you know there's
some questions about um are we going to
get you know what how many states do you
think will actually receive their funds
in 2026?
I
I I think we're we're on track for full
approval. I don't have any we don't have
any indication that um that states won't
receive their deployment funds. I I I
think the outstanding question is what
happens with non-eployment. Um and um
again, I think that there is a role for
all of us to play to continue to talk
about the importance of getting the
deployment funds out the door everywhere
across all 50 states. um and uh continue
to uh communicate the demand uh for the
funding and the need for that funding.
Uh but I think the non the question of
non-employment funding is the is the
open one now and um not only when those
are deployed uh and distributed but also
under what conditions.
So, you know, it wasn't too long ago
there was a big question was were there
really going to be non-eployment funds?
And I think you know, a lot of people
were panicking about some kind of
clawback or something like that. But,
you know, my view and I don't know if
you share this is that non-employment
funds are going to happen. They they
that commerce is committed to deploying
that other 20 whatever it is 21 22
billion dollars for non-employment. Is
that do you share that view?
>> I do. Uh I think the question I mean as
with everything the devil's in the
details um you know we I think like many
states, governors uh state legislators
and members of Congress would have
preferred for um you know those funds to
be the uh clear use of those funds to be
defined now uh for states to be able to
plan uh alongside for implementation of
those funds alongside the deployment
dollars. Um but I I agree. I think that
the um I think commerce is uh sees the
value in uh non-eployment and
particularly as it relates to priorities
like AI uh digital skills training
workforce hopefully fingers crossed um
and all of those things are just going
to extend um the impact of uh this
investment um make sure that those
networks are viable uh really and really
position communities for um I really
hate saying the technology enabled
economy because everything is technology
enabled these days But um really help
position economies for you know to
remain competitive uh or communities to
remain competitive in today's economy.
Um but I I I think again like it it is
uh we hope that there is more
specificity on um the use of those
non-employment funds soon and we're glad
to see that governors all across the
country um including Governor Landry um
you know Governor Yncan have expressed
their support for use of these funds. a
bipartisan cohort of um Congress as you
mentioned has also you know expressed
their support. So let's keep it a
priority people.
Well, absolutely. And you know, in
meeting with um NTIA and Assistant
Secretary Roth, you know, certainly, and
she's said this publicly that um
permitting reform, you know, if you look
at how do we accelerate, you know,
because all these states have to meet a
very short deadline and be able to get
all this money deployed. And you know,
you look at every project um whether
it's broadband or anything, you know, um
having, you know, permitting is such a a
long pole in the tent. And so I'm I'm
very bullish on NTI's ability to, you
know, implement some permitting reform.
I know we worked together, Katherine, on
um our permitting summit and, you know,
put together those recommendations to
Congress. Um we're going to continue
that work to really streamline
permitting and I think there's a great
opportunity to do that. Uh the other you
know as I mentioned along um pull in the
tent is uh workforce you know we've been
fortunate that you know we stood up a
fiber optic technician program called
optic path and now we have over 1,300
graduates and that's accelerating um as
we work to get that program in all 56
states and territories. But, you know,
there's lots of job codes. You know, we
have not only this huge demand in
deployment, but we have a retiring
workforce. And so, you know, those two
things really mean that we need to get
put a lot of people to work, get a lot
of people trained. So, hopefully, you
know, we'll be able to leverage
workforce development. What other uses
do you see, Katherine, for
non-employment funds?
>> Well, uh, I certainly agree with you on
those two, and those were two needs
that, uh, states also identified. So
setting up um you know technical
assistance in state and local government
to help ISPs and their colleagues in the
public sector um address permitting um
needs. And I think the I appreciate uh
Gary you kind of went this direction
already, but adding specificity to what
we mean by the permitting issue or the
workforce issue because a lot of folks
say, "Oh, permitting." And just kind of
throw their hands up and move on. And
our question, as it has been for you as
well, is okay, but what do we mean by
that? Is it federal? Is it state? Is it
local? Where's the roadblock? Is it a
headcount issue? You don't have enough
people to approve permits? Is this a
paperwork issue? Um but I think really
digging into those questions um will be
uh critical in the coming years but also
you know one of the reasons why
non-employment funds to support some of
those learning processes and the systems
to alleviate the barriers would be
really helpful. Agree on workforce um
it's not just fiber slicers it's folks
who can drive trucks it's you know it's
construction at large it's marketing to
help folks adopt the network. Um uh the
other uses we've heard really uh you can
I think kind of lump them together under
um it its uses of um the network itself.
So that's cyber security training, it's
digital skills training including um
helping workers adapt to AI um it's
teleaalth uses. So it really is again
kind of extending the reach of this
investment and ensuring that communities
don't just have these connections
available but they're the economic and
um health and educational benefits are
following alongside them.
You know, the other area that we're
seeing is, you know, the
administration's really pressing on
getting AI and AI infrastructure out the
door. And as everybody on this call
knows, um, fiber, there's a huge demand
for fiber for AI, building out
connecting data centers. And what's
great about that infrastructure is it
delivers middle mile, delivers um long
haul fiber and it also enables
communities to now have uh more cell
towers. So improve their mobile
broadband but also um public safety with
cameras and so forth and smart grid
modernization. So by getting more fiber
out for AI infrastructure is definitely
a great you know investment for those
non-eployment fun you know we'll call
them non-eployment but do deployment of
fiber infrastructure for AI and just the
economic development impact of that is
huge
>> you guys agree with that
>> absolutely I I think the connection I
I'm want to pull exactly what you just
said so we could uh adapt that quote
because I think exactly how how you just
explained it um making helping folks
understand the connection between the
fiber buildout and AI and public safety
that uh that connection is not always
there folks sometimes you really need to
help um you need to draw that line so um
policy makers and other folks uh
understand like oh you really do need
this fiber to be out in the ground for
these other um needs to um for these for
other needs and purposes. Like you can't
you can't update public safety, you
can't update the grid unless you have
that robust fiber backbone bone there
and AI thankfully gives us a really easy
um way to describe that. Um but I that
is one thing that I worry about at times
is um we can't lose sight of what needs
to be built even as we are thinking
ahead um for AI and all these other
applications in the future.
You know, one of the questions that here
I'll take is um you know, what are we
going to do about a potential fiber
shortage slowing down the pace of fiber
deployment? Um it seems to be this is
talked about a lot on the ground. So
just to kind of peel this back, um
there's manufacturers that actually make
the glass that draw the glass and then
it goes that's resold to a number of
companies that c actually put it into
the the fiber cables. Um so while AI is
taking a huge amount of fiber the bead
requirements actually don't come off the
back end but they are the first that are
prioritized and if you look at bead is
for rural um low density areas and so
that would be cabled in something called
loose tube and so when we look at loose
tube um there's a lot of availability
more than enough for um addressing all
the feed requirements where there is
long lead times that's on what's called
ribbon cable and that is you know for
what we're seeing for more highdensity
applications like AI um now some
companies like to just standardize on
one type of fiber for make it easier but
um again these are things that we look
at every day we have a supply chain
working group uh we meet with all all
the fiber manufacturers and make things
to stay on track so I think we're in
pretty good shape but you know there's
certainly
What I told NTI is when we went from
kind of a nice ramp to a shotgun start
with all 56 states and territories kind
of starting at once, that does give a
shock to the supply chain. But our
studies show that, you know, we had this
huge surplus where everybody was
hoarding fiber coming out of COVID, then
service fighters stopped buying and
worked that inventory down. Um, now
we're at equilibrium, so we're at a good
spot to start. Um, all right. All right.
Well, let me just make sure I hit
anything um before we have to exit here
because I know that um so one of the
questions is
why can't um operators use their bead
funds for operations versus just
deployment
>> statute.
the the law the it's it's been explicit
that these are for capital expenditures
and not uh operating expenditures.
>> All right. Well, we have a ton a ton of
questions, but um let's just close on
two things. One, I want to hear your New
Year's resolution,
and two, I want to hear what you're most
optimistic about in 2026.
>> Gary, are we are we are we going to
trade like lifting notes right now? we
talk about strength training the
resolution for 2026 I think for
everybody
uh um we uh we've got a big year ahead
of us uh for uh my team at Pew. Uh so my
resolution is just uh is really feeling
good about that roll out of new work and
um making sure that we're keep
maintaining our focus which is the
support for the states and strength
training as I mentioned. Uh and uh I
think um what am I feeling optimistic
about? Um
we're moving forward. I think that the
uh the last 12 months have been uh
filled with a lot of uncertainty and
changes. Um but NTIA is approving state
plans. NIST is approving things. Uh and
uh states actually are poised to break
grounds on projects this year. That is
really exciting. And despite the changes
um and a lot of the concern when those
changes were announced, we know that the
majority of locations that will be
funded by bead will receive fiber. This
is a big deal. It means that the we are
going to narrow the availability gap in
ways that we have not been able to
contemplate. Um so I'm very optimistic
about that. Um I think I'm also just I'm
very optimistic about state leadership.
I mean we talked about this at the top
but states are engaged in ways that they
haven't been before. Um, and they want
to solve the availability challenge
because they need it for all of those
economic development needs. They need
it. They experience these gaps in a way,
I think, differently than a lot of us in
DC understand. Um, they understand the
economic imperative and SBOs's, they
just keep doing the work. The directors
uh and their teams, they're just
fighting uh for connectivity. Um, even
as those new challenges and uh
opportunities emerge, they're rolling
with it. and I am constantly impressed
by their creativity, their technical
expertise, and their savvy. So, trust
the states. Uh, and we can all work
together to get this over the finish
line.
>> Well, Katherine, as always, I love
talking with you, love your insights. I
love the support. I love everything you
do and your group does to support the
SPOS's. And speaking of state broadband
offices, next Wednesday we have our good
friend Brandy Ritter, the executive
director of the Colorado State Broadband
Office, going to be here to discuss from
strategy to sustainability, Colorado's
broadband approach to reliability and
reach. Um, just spent my uh holiday
skiing in Colorado with no snow. So, I'm
anxious to see what uh Brandy has to
say. And uh, Katherine, I can't wait to
see you at our conference. I can't wait
for our conference. It's I mean the guys
have really pulled out all the stops.
It's going to be so huge and so awesome
especially the AI infrastructure summit
that's going to be hosted by my favorite
quantum physicist Mitchio Kaku. So I
hope you guys are there in Orlando in
May. Katherine have a I look forward to
seeing you in DC here in probably next
week.
>> I hope so.
>> You guys soon.
>> Thank you again for having me.
>> All right. Thanks everyone. Thanks for
joining us today.